A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1972-2012
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence, subject files and board meeting records (Accession 51080), 1972-1997., Extent: 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes).
  - Housing and Coummunity Development - Low Income Housing Tax Credit Program, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Housing and Coummunity Development - Low Income Housing Tax Credit: Wellesley Woods Project, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Housing and Coummunity Development - 60 day letter, 19 (Box 4)
  - Housing and Coummunity Development - Virginia Community Development Corporation, 1994 Oct-1995 Dec (Box 4)
  - Mental Health - Governor's Office correspondence, 1994 May-1995 June (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth, Secretary of the, 1994-1995 (Box 4)
  - General Assembly, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Legislation - Correspondence, 1993 Jan (Box 4)
  - Legislation - Correspondence, 1993 Feb (Box 4)
  - Legislation - Meetings with legislators, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Legislation - Appointments with legislators, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Services, 1994-1995 (Box 4)
  - Housing Study Commission, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Housing Study Commission - Work Session, 1993 (Box 4)
  - U.S. - Farmers Home Administration, 1994-1995 (Box 4)
  - U.S. - Dept. of Housing and Urban Development, 1994-1995 (Box 4)
  - U.S. - Dept. of Housing and Urban Development - Region III, Philadelphia, 1994-1995 (Box 4)
  - U.S. - Dept. of Housing and Urban Development - Richmond Area Office, 1994 Oct-1995 Sept (Box 4)
  - U.S. - Dept. of Housing and Urban Development - HUD Program Descriptions, 1994-1995 (Box 4)
  - Executive Division: Director, 1995 July-1996 June (Box 4)
  - Executive Division: Correspondence (chronological), 1995 July-1996 June (Box 4)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners, 1995 July-1996 June (Box 4)
  - Executive Division: Expense Reports, 1995-1996 June (Box 4)
  - Executive Division: HOME meeting, 1996 May 21 (Box 4)
  - Executive Division: Southwest Virginia Visits Comm. Krum, 1996 Aug (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Board Retreat survey results, 1994-1996 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: U.S, Legislators, 1995 July-1996 June (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: State Legislators, 1995 July-1996 June (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Meetings and Speaking Engagements, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Board Retreat, 1995 Mar (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Board Retreat, 1995 Nov (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Board Retreat, 1996 Mar (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Bond Allocation, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Fund Balance Study, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Problem Loans, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Multifamily Delinquencies, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: General Counsel, 1995July-1996 June (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Single Family Loans to VHDA employees, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Multifamily, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Director, 1995 July-1996 June (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: LIHTC Program, 19June95 July-1996 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Staff Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Planning and Research, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Suffolk RHA, 19 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Single Family, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Meetings with Lyn Williams, 1993-1994 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Commerce and Trade, Secretary of, 1994-1995 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: General correspondence, 1995 July-1996 June (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Communications, 19 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Weekly Reports, 1995 July-1996 June (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Mental Health, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Attorney General, 1995-1996 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Washington Liaison Office, 1995-1996 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Housing Study Commission, 1994 July-Dec (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services: Director, 1995 July-1996 June (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services: Memo on Kelly Retirement, 1994 Dec (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Director, 1996 July-1997 June (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Accomplishments, 1994-1995 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Articles of interest, 1996 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Executive Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Business Plan, 1994-1995 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Measurements, 1994-1997 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Off-site EC meeting, 1995 July 1 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Strategic Planning, 1992-1994 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Stragetic Action Plan, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners, 1996 July-1997 June (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners - Expense Reports, 1996 July-Dec (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners - Board Committees, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners - Orientation, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners - Cheryl J. Avery-Hargrove, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners - J. Stephen Britt, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners - Pablo Cuevas, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners - Tracey S. DeBoissiere, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners - Susan F. Dewey, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners - Sam Kornblau, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners - Charles L. Krum, Jr., 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners - Micheal G. Miller, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners - Michael J. Schewel, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners - Warren C. Smith, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners - Commissioners' Update, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: U.S. Legislators, 1996 July-1997 June (Box 7)
  - Executive Division: State Legislators, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Executive Division: Meeting wit Senator Andrews, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Executive Division: Fall Board Retreat, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Executive Division: Nonprofit Housing Groups, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Executive Division: Director, 1997 Jan-June (Box 7)
  - Legal Division, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of, 1996 July-1997 June (Box 7)
  - Commerece and Trade, Secretary of - Weekly Reports, 1996 July-1997 June (Box 7)
  - Finance, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Mental Health, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Govenor's Office, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Governor's Office - Executive Orders, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
  - Legislative, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - General Assembly, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Housing Study Commission, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Housing and Urban Development, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Housing and Urban Developoment - Central Office, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - Housing and Urban Development - Virginia Ownership Strategy, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Housing and Urban Development - Richmond Area Office, 1996 July-1997 June (Box 7)
- Correspondence, subject files and board meeting records (Accession 52645), 1999-2012., Extent: 5 cu. ft. (5 boxes).
  - House Finance Committee Presentation, 2004 Jan (Box 1)
  - House Finance Committee Presentation, 2006 Jan (Box 1)
  - House Finance Committee Presentation, 2006 June (Box 1)
  - House Finance Committee Presentation, 2008 Jan (Box 1)
  - House Finance Committee Presentation, 2008 Aug (Box 1)
  - Virginia Housing Commission, 2007 Apr (Box 1)
  - Virginia Housing Commission, 2007 Sept (Box 1)
  - Board Meeting and Retreat - Issue Briefs, 2010 Apr (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting and Retreat, 2009 Apr (Box 2)
  - Board Retreat, 2009 Mar (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting, 2009 Feb (Box 2)
  - Board Retreat, 2009 (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting, 2009 June (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting, 2009 Aug (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting, 2009 Oct (Box 2)
  - Board Meeting, 2009 Dec (Box 2)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2009 Feb (Box 3)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2009 June (Box 3)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2009 Aug (Box 3)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2009 Oct (Box 3)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2009 Dec (Box 3)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2010 Feb (Box 3)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2010 Apr (Box 3)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2010 June (Box 3)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2011 Apr (Box 3)
  - Board Retreat, 2011 Apr (Box 3)
  - Annual Meeting, 2010 Aug (Box 3)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2010 Oct (Box 3)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2010 Dec (Box 3)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2011 Feb (Box 3)
  - Board Retreat, 2011 Apr (Box 3)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2008 Feb (Box 4)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2008 Apr (Box 4)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2008 May (Box 4)
  - Annual Board Meeting, 2008 Aug (Box 4)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2008 Oct (Box 4)
  - Regualr Board Meeting, 2008 Dec (Box 4)
  - Section 8 Program review, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Foreclosure Prevention Task Force - Organizational meeting, 2007 Dec (Box 5)
  - Virginia Foreclosure Task Force meetings, 2011 (Box 5)
  - VHDA Analysis of Accounting Dept. operations - Reznick, Fedder and Silverman, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Setting a Housing Policy Agenda - Meeting, 2006 Oct (Box 5)
  - Virginia Housing Commission presentations, 2009-2011 (Box 5)
  - VHDA Associate Survey Report, 2008 (Box 5)
  - Executive Director's Notes on Board Meetings, 2010-2011 (Box 5)
  - VHDA Hokie Memorial Scholarship, 2007 (Box 5)
  - Governor's Management Standards Scorecard, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Governor's Management Standards Scorecard, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Commerce and Trade Strategic Plan (VHDA Strategic Plan submitted by to Secretary Michael J. Schewel), 2003 (Box 5)
  - Briefing for the Office of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, Matthew S. Erskine, 2002 Oct (Box 5)
  - Planning Team notes, 2009 (Box 5)
  - New Initiatives Briefings, 2001 Dec (Box 5)
  - House Finance Committee Presentations, 2009-2012 (Box 5)
  - Executive Director's copies of Board Meeting materials, 2012 (Box 5)
- Correspondence, subject files and board meeting records (Accession 52931), 1997-2012 (bulk 2011-2012)., Extent: 3 cu. ft. (3 boxes).
  - Development MF LIHTC Program, 2011 (Box 1)
  - REACH Team, 2011 (Box 1)
  - SF Development, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Director, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Commissioner's Update, 2009 (Box 1)
  - U.S. Legislators, 2011 (Box 1)
  - State Legislators, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Nonprofit Housing Groups, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Internal Auditor / General Auditor / KPMG, 2011 (Box 1)
  - General Counsel, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Servicing and Compliance, 2011 (Box 1)
  - SF Servicing and Compliance, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Special Programs - HCVP, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Special Programs - HUD Commonwealh of Virginia, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Executive Commerce and Trade correspondence, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Leadership Team minutes, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Leadership Team agendas and minutes, 2008-2011 (Box 1)
  - VHDA Five-Year Business Planning, 1997-2001 (Box 1)
  - Board Retreat / Meetings (Susan Dewey), 2000 Oct; 2006 (Box 1)
  - MF Asset Management, 2012 (Box 2)
  - MF LIHTC Program, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Programs Team meetings, 2012 (Box 2)
  - REACH Team, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Single Family Development, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Director, 2012 (Box 2)
  - U.S. Legislators, 2012 (Box 2)
  - State Legislators, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Views at Clarendon, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Buchanan Gardent grand opening, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Nonprofit Housing Groups, 2012 (Box 2)
  - VAR, 2012 (Box 2)
  - VCEE, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Director, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Audit follow-up, 2012 (Box 2)
  - General Counsel, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Reorganization, 2012 (Box 2)
  - ODL Director, 2012 (Box 2)
  - PPC Stategic Planning, 2012 (Box 2)
  - S and C SF Servicing and Compliance, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Constituent inquiries - Servicing (A-F), 2012 (Box 2)
  - Constituent inquiries - Servicing (G-L), 2012 (Box 2)
  - Constituent inquiries - Servicing (M-S), 2012 (Box 2)
  - Constituent inquiries - Servicing (T-Z), 2012 (Box 2)
  - S and C SP / HCPV, 2012 (Box 2)
  - S and C SP / HUD, 2012 (Box 2)
  - Commerce and Trade, 2012 (Box 2)
  - S and C - General correspondence, 2012 Jan-June (Box 2)
  - S and C - General correspondence, 2012 July-December (Box 2)
  - Commerce and Trade weekly reports, 2012 (Box 2)
  - DHCD general correspondence, 2012 (Box 3)
  - Governor's Office general correspondence, 2012 (Box 3)
  - ED LT meeting notes, 2012 (Box 3)
  - ED Direct reports / progress notes, 2012 (Box 3)
- Correspondence, subject files and board meeting records (Accession 53435), 2015-2018., Extent: 3 cu. ft. (3 boxes).
  - Check requests, 2017 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Check requests, 2017 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Expense reports, 2017 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - , 2017 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Leadership Team working agendas and notes, 2017 Jan-Mar (Box 1)
  - Leadership Team working agendas and notes, 2017 Apr-June (Box 1)
  - Leadership Team working agendas and notes, 2017 July-Sept (Box 1)
  - Leadership Team working agendas and notes, 2017 Oct-Dec (Box 1)
  - Community Outreach: for Managing Director, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Community Outreach: Grant Programs and Initiatives, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Community Outreach: Housing Choice Voucher Program (HCVP), 2017 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Community Outreach: Marketing, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Community Outreach: Policy and Research, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Community Outreach: Meeting Thomas Jacobson re: VCU Affordable Housing Study, 2017 Sept (Box 1)
  - Community Outreach: Strategic Housing and Program Implementation, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Chronological correspondence, 2017 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Executive: Chronological correspondence, 2017 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Executive: Compensation Committee meetings, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Commissioners - General, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Business Initiatives and Resource Planning (BIRP) meetings, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Executive Services, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Internal audit, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Legislative Liaison, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Weekly legislative meetings, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Executive: U.S. Legislators, 2017 June (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Miscellaneous, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - SunTrust / Home Ownership discussion, 2017 Jan 4 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Fostering Affordable and Sustainable Home Ownership with SunTrust Mortgate, 2017 Jan 24 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Community Land Trust presentation, 2017 Feb 7 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Virginia Association of Realtors Legislative Reception at the Jefferson Hotel, 2017 Feb 8 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Better Housing Coalition meeting, 2017 Feb 9 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - GSE Duty to Service listening sessions, 2017 Feb 9 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Caritas - 14th Annual Celebrity Service, 2017 Feb 21 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Arlington Partnership for Affordable Housing (APAH) strategic planning call, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Judson McKellar, 2017 Apr 10 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Union on Queen Grand Opening, 2017 Apr 26 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Liberty Ribbon Cutting - Lorton Prison, 2017 May 18 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Bruce Hazelgrove / New Market, 2017 June 13 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Virginia Housing Alliance Awards Luncheon, 2017 June 15 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Northern Virginia Advisory meeting, 2017 June 19 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Excellence in Virgina Government Awards Committee breakfast meeting, 2017 June 16 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Housing Associaton of Non-Profit Developers (HAND) Annual Meeting and Housing Expo, 2017 June 20 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Virginia Housing Alliance (VHA) Most Vulnerable Conference, 2017 Aug 16 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Woda's Grand Opening for Brennan Point, 2017 Aug 31 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Tennessee Housing Development Board Retreat, 2017 Sept 25 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Virginia Mortgage Lenders Association (VMLA) Annual Convention, 2017 Sept 21-22 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Disability Law Center of Virginia General Open House, 2017 Oct 26 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Housing Association of Non-Profit Developers (HAND) Member Forum on Local Real Estate Trends and Market Conditions, 2017 Nov 1 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Southeastern States Tax Credit Conference, 2017 Nov 5-7 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engatments - Board Retreat, 2016 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Leadership Team Retreat, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Advisory Boards, 2017 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Advisory Boards, 2017 July-Dec (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Home Ownership Advisory Board, 2017 May 4 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Rural Housing Adviory Council, 2017 Oct 17 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Virgina Association of Realtors Annual Conference, 2017 Oct 3-5 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Virginia Bankers Association Finance Forecast meeting, 2017 Jan 6 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - VCU Real Estate Trends Conference, 2017 Oct 12 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Meetings / Speaking Engagements - Virginia Council on Economic Education Board, 2017 Mar 21 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Virginia Association of Realtors (VAR), 2017 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Virginia Bankers Association (VBA), 2017 (Box 2)
  - Executive: VCU Real Estate Circle of Excellence, 2017 Jan-June (Box 2)
  - Executive: VCU Real Estate Circle of Excellence, 2017 July-Dec (Box 2)
  - Executive: Virginia Council on Economic Education (VCEE), 2017 Jan-Apr (Box 2)
  - Executive: Bond allocation, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Board, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Board meeting, 2017 Aug 8 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Local Initiative Support Corporation, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Non-Profit Housing Groups, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Venture Richmond Annual Meeting, 2017 Apr 6 (Box 2)
  - Executive: William and Mary Foundation Board, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Bond Refunding / Treasurer, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Controller / Accounting / Budget / Procurement, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Controller / Accounting / Budget / Procurement: Projected (2017) / Proposed Budgets (2018), 2017 (Box 2)
  - Controller / Accounting / Budget / Procurement: Moody and S/P rating letters, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Home Ownership: Managing Director, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Home Ownership: Golf Tournament, 2017 May (Box 2)
  - Home Ownership: Servicing Constituent Inquiries (A-Z), 2017 (Box 2)
  - Home Ownership: ProTeam, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Home Ownership: Lending Programs, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Human Resources: Managing Director, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Human Resources: Management Forum meetings, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Human Resources: Training / Employment Services, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Rental Housing: Managing Director, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Rental Housing: Low-Income Housing Tax Credit Program (LIHTC), 2017 (Box 2)
  - Rental Housing: ProTeam, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Risk: Managing Director, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Risk: Audited Financials, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources - Spring HSS Leadership Planning meeting, 2017 June 12 (Box 2)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Governor's Office, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Governor's Office - Meeting with Noah Sullivan, Deputy Counsel to Gov. McAuliffe, 2017 Apr 10 (Box 2)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) - Central Correspondence, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Federal correspondence, 2017 (Box 2)
  - National Council of State Housing Agencies, 2017 (Box 2)
  - National Council of State Housing Agencies - Board meetings, 2017 (Box 2)
  - National Council of State Housing Agencies - Legislative Conference, 2017 (Box 2)
  - National Council of State Housing Agencies - Workshop, 2017 (Box 2)
  - National Council of State Housing Agencies - Other HFAs, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Secretary of Commerce and Trade - Gov. McAuliffe's Housing Policy, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of - General correspondence, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of - Board meetings, 2017 (Box 2)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of - VH Quarterly Meeting, 2017 Dec 4 (Box 3)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of - VH Quarterly Meeting, 2017 Oct 2 (Box 3)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of - VH Home Loans meeting, 2017 Oct 16 (Box 3)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of - Housing Study invoice, 2017 (Box 3)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of - Universities Prep for Housing Policy Advisory Council (HPAC) meeting, 2017 (Box 3)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of - Housing Policy, 2017 (Box 3)
  - Finance / State Treasurer, 2017 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director Approval Requests, 2018 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director Approval Requests, 2017 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director Approval Requests, 2016 (Box 3)
  - Executive Director Approval Requests, 2015 (Box 3)
  - Housing Policy Advisory Council (HPAC), 2016 (Box 3)
  - Governor's Office - General Correspondence and Proclamation, 2016 (Box 3)
  - Governor's Office - Visit, 2016 June 13 (Box 3)
  - Governor's Office: Governor McAuliffe's Housing Policy, 2016 (Box 3)
  - Governor's Housing Conference, 2017 Nov 15 (Box 3)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of - Meeting to discuss Housing Policy Advisory Council (HPAC) Subcommittees, 2016 Apr 20 (Box 3)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of - Housing Policy Advisory Council (HPAC) University Call, 2016 Apr 20 (Box 3)